question_d = [{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a "
                         "QWERTY keyboard.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
             "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States "
                         "conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s "
                         "life expectancy.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot;"
                         " is a grammatically correct sentence.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
